残酷な天使のように 少年よ 神話になれ
青い風が今 胸のドアを叩いても 私だけをただ見つめて 微笑んでるあなた
そっと触れるもの 求めることに夢中で 運命さえまだ知らない 痛い気な瞳
だけどいつか気づくでしょう その背中には
遥か未来 目指すための羽があること
残酷な天使の帝世 窓辺からやがて飛ぶたつ
もっと走る熱いパッドスで 思い出を裏切るなら
この空を抱いて輝く 少年よ 神話になれ
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Although there was a great deal of damage as a result, the fact that Shinji Ikaru, a boy with no prior EVA experience, managed to accomplish the mission against an unknown enemy, deserves special notice.
However, for the Department of Strategic Operations, it was a difficult battle that would reveal many problem areas that were in desperate need of improvement.
I can't believe it.
My sister's only in second grade. She got hurt in that stupid battle in the city. What makes it worse is that she was injured by her own stupid robot, not by the enemy.
There's no way I can forgive anyone who did something so stupid.
I'm gonna find the jerks who hurt my sister and teach them a lesson they'll never forget.
We'd already had a lot of evacuation training at the school, so we didn't really think it was that serious.
The guys were all acting like jerks as usual, like they were on a field trip, and none of the girls were afraid either.
We spooned it with his children after coming again.
The organizing group took its skills later...
The work that our enemy took was cat.
It was that way of having their único дома at home as I went to the school, right?
Thank you.
This is Rey herself.
I don't think she has much respect for her own existence.
She's not just pessimistic.
Hell, a lot of kids our age are like that.
No, it's something much, much more.
But nobody ever tells me nothing.
This event did not occur in accordance with our scenario, Ikari.
Nevertheless, the result was within the projected parameters.
We can make the necessary adjustments.
The United Nations combined Navy lost one-third of its entire fleet in this encounter.
At least the lost ships belong to your country.
The damage is negligible.
Quite true.
It was fortunate that so much of the damage was inconsequential.
You're lucky to have gone on the floor right now.
The number of locations that went on...
... clique sets off the floor of the sky, I think, really...
.
of
the
Lily too.
Ha ha ha!
learners
can
you
is
Arvind!
Arvind Eren!
Arvind.
I don't know.
Good. It's happening too early.
Yes. This did not occur in accordance with our predictions of when an Angel would invade, no.
And to make it worse, you let it intrude into Central Dogma itself.
If contact had occurred, then our entire project could have ended in disaster, Ikari.
The report to this committee was in error. There is no fact behind this tale of an Angel invasion.
Ikari, are you saying that the 11th Angel's intrusion never occurred?
Yes.
Watch your words carefully, Ikari. Lying to this committee is perishable by death.
If you wish confirmation, check the Magi's data recorders. No such incident was ever recorded.
This is absurd. We all know that bearing the truth is your specialty.
The time schedule is being carried out in accordance with the descriptions in the Dead Sea Scrolls.
All right. We won't discuss any possible guilt or punishment this time.
However, let me remind you that you won't rewrite our scenario.
I understand. Everything is proceeding according to Saleh's plan.
Mountains.
Heavy are the mountains.
But that changes.
With the passage of time.
Sky.
Loose sky.
What your eyes can't see.
What your eyes can see.
The sun.
One.
Only one.
Water.
It is agreeable.
Commander Ikari.
Flowers.
So many the same.
So many without purpose.
Sky.
Sky of red.
Red the color.
The color I hate.
The liquid flows.
It drips, ripples and pours.
Blood.
A scent of blood.
A woman who does not bleed.
From the red soil the humans come.
Humans made by man and woman.
City.
A human creation.
Ava.
A human creation as well.
What are humans?
Are they creations of God?
Humans.
That which is created by humans.
This is that which is mine.
My life.
My heart.
I am a vessel for my thoughts.
The entry club.
Throne of the soul.
Who is this?
This is me.
Who am I?
What am I?
I am I.
This object that is, is myself.
That which forms, is me.
This is the self that can be seen and yet this is not like that which is myself.
A strange feeling.
My body feels as if it is melting.
I can no longer see myself.
My form, my shape fades from view.
Awareness dawns of someone who is not me.
Who is here, there, beyond me here.
Shinji.
This person I know, Major Katsuragi.
Dr. Akaki.
People.
My classmates.
The pilot of Unit 2.
Commander Ikari.
Who are you?
So, Ray, how does it feel to be piloting Unit 1 for the first time?
Smells like Ikari.
The sync ratio is almost the same as with Unit 0.
Unit 0 and Unit 1's personal data patterns are almost identical.
That's what makes this sync experiment possible.
Error margin is 0.03.
Harmonics are normal.
No detectable problems found for compatibility between Ray and Unit 1.
Okay, the test is over, Ray.
You can get out now.
Yes.
Unit 2 data bank completed.
Harmonics are all normal.
Pilot status is normal.
Of course I'm normal.
What about Unit 0's personal data?
Already reconfigured.
Reconfirming data now.
Subject status?
A bit jittery, but no problems found in the nerve patterns.
This is his first time in Unit 0.
His first time piloting another Ava.
It's only natural.
That's stupid.
Why should he care which Ava he's in anyway?
It makes a difference to Shinji.
That's how he is.
I know that.
He's such a dork.
So why aren't you running these compatibility tests on me?
Is there something wrong with me?
Well, we didn't think he'd want to pilot any Ava except yours.
Yeah, that's true, isn't it?
I don't know if Unit 2 would even be compatible.
Beginning entry.
LCL electrolyzed.
Commence Earth connection.
Shinji, how do you feel in Unit 0?
How's entry plug?
Uh, it feels kind of weird.
Like incompatibility?
Not like that.
This thing smells like rain.
It smells like what?
That's a mensch.
Data received.
Reconfirming.
Pattern green.
All restraints are nominal.
Acknowledged.
Now let's shift the mutual compatibility test to the second stage.
Unit 0, entering second contact.
How's it look?
As I thought, the sync ratio is lower than that of Unit 1.
Hmm, harmonics are all normal.
But these are still good readings.
These numbers mean that we can implement our current plan.
You mean the tummy system?
Ma'am, I'm really not sure that we should proceed.
I understand your feelings on this, but we always have to be prepared for all options.
It's our guarantee of survival.
You know that I've always respected you, ma'am, and I still believe in our work.
But I'm afraid I'm really not convinced.
People who develop too many scruples will always have some difficulty working amongst others.
You'll learn once you've gotten your hands dirty.
You'll see.
Initiate third connection.
Self-state of Minecraft is stable.
It's Shinji missing Mama's breath.
Has it like being in her womb or what?
Asuka, stop interrupting.
You're being obnoxious.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't get it.
Why does everyone around here always pamper him?
Commence A-10 nerve connections.
Harmonics level, plus 20.
What the hell?
Something's trying to get into my brain.
Ray?
Ray Ayanami?
This feeling, impression.
Ray, it's hers.
What's happening?
There's a problem in the pilot's nerve pulse.
Mental contamination starting.
Impossible.
This can't happen at this plug depth.
It's not from the plug.
The intrusion is coming from the angle.
Unit zero is out of control.
Shut all circuits.
Cut the power.
Ava has switched to reserve power.
Ava is still activated.
Shinji status.
The circuit's closed.
We can't monitor him.
Unit zero is rejecting Shinji.
Negative.
The auto-ejection.
It doesn't work.
The same error.
The same one.
Is it trying to absorb Shinji?
Ray, get back here.
Ray!
Activation will terminate in seven seconds.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Activation terminated.
Hurry up and get the pilot out of there.
Did unit zero just try to kill Ray?
Do you think this could be related to the incident that occurred when Ray was the pilot?
I can't tell you much right now.
The only thing I'm sure of is that we must reconfigure unit zero for Ray's personal data
and run a new synchronization test between Ray and the zero as soon as possible.
As the director of operations, I request that it be done as soon as possible before there
are further problems.
I understand that, Major Katsuragi.
Right.
Unit zero wanted to attack me.
That's got to be it.
Huh?
Again, I hate this ceiling.
The hospital says Shinji has regained consciousness.
No signs of mental contamination.
But he doesn't remember what happened.
Right.
Misato and Kashi won't tell me anything about her.
Even Shinji doesn't know anything.
Just what is the first child?
The Angels' evasion of headquarters was a deviation from our scheduled scenario.
The committees found out about it and are applying pressure.
They're buzzing around our heads like a swarm of hornets, looking for things to complain about.
We hold all the tiles, all the winds and dragons.
There is nothing they can do.
That doesn't mean we want to keep tipping our hand.
If Sele starts to interfere, there could be trouble.
Everything is going according to the scenario.
No problems exist.
What about the unit zero incident?
Hmm?
That was not in our scenario.
It will have no effect.
Ray's resynchronization test was successful.
You're too concerned about protecting Ray, Akari?
Uh, what's the status of the Adam project?
Proceeding.
It's less than 2% behind schedule.
Then the lands of Longinus is...
Is going according to plan.
Ray is handling the operation.
Fly me to the moon
And let me play among the stars
Let me see where spring
Feels like I'm Jupiter and Mars
In other worlds
Hold my hand
Darling, kiss me
Fill my heart with song
And let me sing forevermore
You are all I love
For all I love
Superdome
In other worlds
Please be true
I love you
With her friends getting married one after another
Misato starts to feel a little insecure
Always a bridesmaid
She might just end up spinning the rest of her life
Going to wedding showers
And never finding anyone for herself
Could a reunion with Kashi be her last chance?
In the next episode
The old biological clock goes
St conflicting
honest
To be honest
You're welcome
You can find food
Whoim spots
Where
You know
Came to dream
Come on
You can find food
That yet
You know
I mean
You can find aimmune
findet
Like
I Hollow machen